Time 24
Energy 100
Efficiancy 100
Creativity 150
Communication 50
Programming 100
Motivation 80


A casual gamer is a player whose time or interest in playing games is limited.
 Casual gamers tend to play games designed for ease of gameplay and don't spend much time playing more involved games.
 The genres that casual gamers play vary, and they might not own a specific video game console to play their games.
Casual gamer demographics vary greatly from those of other video gamers, as the typical casual gamer is older and more predominantly female.